WORK EXPERIENCE



VIdeo Editor

Audio Visual UGTV (Full Time) September 2020 - September 2022 (2

September 2020 - September 2022 (2 Years)

- I made videos for all TV programs
- I made a campus profile video
- I made Animated videos for big events on TV programs
- I made a video about Tourism



Video Editor, Motion Graphic

Yayasan Generasi Maju Berkarya

April 2022 - Present

- Make learning videos every month for the education team
- Make Reels, Youtube and tiktok videos for the marketing team
- create motion asset templates to make videos more interesting

EDUCATION HISTORY



Bachelor of Tourism, Major in Destination University of Gunadarma

2018 - 2022

- Cum Laude
- Full scholarship student Program
- · Lab Assistant of Audio Visual

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Currently, as a worker who has a background in tourism, I am equipped with the knowledge of how to develop tourism in a place, then packaged as attractively as possible following the times, that's why I packaged it in a Videography and Photography Concept. I have skills in Video Editing, Videography and Photography, where I got those skills during 3 years working in the Broadcasting world.



Devian Kharisma

Video Editor



Portfolio Link

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1dY7YWhaXw1mY-uBiiAV3n6-flzQ3295U/view

CONTACT ME

linkedin.com/in/devian-kharisma-580122206/deviankharisma@gmail,com 0895330975834

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe After Effect
- Motion Graphics
- Davinci Resolve
- Photography
- Videography